testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Oh, is it because you can't see this?
Ah, the three of them worked hard to prepare this, so like this
Hello.
Wait a sec. First
I'm going to look at the comments.
Yeah.
Hello.
It feels really nice having it all set up like this.
Isn't the cake so pretty?
It's pretty up close, right?
Today is my birthday
Me too, it's cute.
Should I put it here? Like this.
Ah, but I want to take a picture first.
I do want to take a picture.
I'll just take a picture.
It's cute.
Whoa, it's cute.
I like it. Ah, let me just take one selfie with it.
I have to take a selfie. Yeah, sorry, before I eat it.
Done.
Let's really start the birthday party now like this. Flover
I'll put it in like this
Should we light the candle?
Then, you're ready, right?
Here I go.
Look.
Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to me.
Now, I'll lift it up.
Now, like this
I also blew out the candle.
I look pretty today. What was it today? I told the makeup artist
please do it nicely since it's my birthday. That's what I said.
I'll be inside and then go to the Kangnam University festival later. So inside here
I'm wearing my top.
If you want to know what it looks like
It's like this
Should I have a little taste?
Since it's not visible, from the back
I'll scoop it first and
It's so good. It's delicious.
It tastes like cream cheese. It's a flavor I like.
It's good. The inside is whipped cream. Ah,
It's amazing. Mm. It's delicious.
Isn't this just a mukbang?
Today's glory goes to
If I eat this much you can't tell from the front, right? How much I ate.
It's really good. I ate this much.
I didn't eat a lot.
How is it? I got a bit closer.
I'm pretty. Thanks.
Capture time.
A lot
Exactly puffy
Rather than just doing puffy cheeks like this
putting air in my cheeks is cuter.
Like this.
I haven't eaten yet. Won't I eat when I go home after this?
Oh the chat is so fast. It puts me in a good mood today.
The comments are so fast. I feel good.
Since it's my birthday, Flover, press the hearts hard.
Press the hearts a whole lot.
Work hard for me today.
Even if the comments actually stop
you're saying there's no chat because you're pressing hearts
What the?
What's with reaching 1 million? Flover is overworking today.
Ah, thinking about Flover pressing hearts
is so cute.
Man, this is the best birthday.
You're asking if I don't have a candle today? I do.
It's been so long since I did a birthday live I don't remember what we talked about but
what do people usually talk about on birthday lives?
What did we talk about?
We say fun things, right? That balance game
Please play the balance game.
Between the mountain and the sea
This really changes a lot originally I really thought mountain
but these days I think it's the sea.
The sea
I want to go. Let's go to the sea. The sea
If I go there's that beach
and the sound of the waves you know. When I hear that sound
I like it because it feels like things become peaceful.
Why I originally liked the mountain was
because I like the smell of grass so
I think that's why I liked it. Now
I'm in the bathroom and I hear people outside talking trash about me. Do I go out or not.
I won't go out.
Mm. But I think I'd peek through the gap in the bathroom stall door like who is it?
Like that.
Who is that?
And
I think I'd be really upset.
But really if I hear someone talking trash behind my back
Ah I really don't like talking behind people's backs.
So when I heard someone talking behind my back I
wasn't confident I could forgive them. Why do that behind my back? But
I saw a video a while ago I saw it in the past
maybe it was last year but it said if I
hate that person what was it it's been a while but if I hate them
it just hurts my own heart so
whether they do that behind my back or not
they said it's good to have a heart that can forgive.
I just didn't have the courage to forgive like that.
Garlic vs onion I'm unconditionally garlic
I like raw garlic but I can't eat raw onions
So somehow
But before a fansign if I eat meat I always eat raw garlic
you know. That's how it feels like eating meat. But
I can't go around reeking of smell at a fansign. Like crazy.
Because of that I hold back. From garlic.
Well, if the person I'm eating with eats it together
it's allowed but if I eat it alone I can't talk then.
Go back 10 years vs meet myself 10 years in the future. I really
think about this a lot
Usually it was always going back 10 years but as time goes by
I started thinking it'd be better to go 10 years into the future. If I go back
10 years
all the things
I've worked so hard on
they would all disappear just like that. So
I thought I want to go 10 years into the future.
When I go back 10 years I don't even know if I'd be able to debut
with fromis_9 or not. So I
like the present so I cherish it and think
it would be better to just go to the future instead.
Ah
Buy stocks no like go back to the past and buy stocks
No if I do that
it might be nice but
Egg fried rice vs Kimchi fried rice. Oh, I used to be unconditionally Kimchi fried rice but
kind of a mild egg fried rice has its own charm.
How about Flover? Just taking egg fried rice and
not frying the kimchi with it but just raw kimchi
placed on top makes it feel somehow tastier. These days
I really love dumplings. Lately what I always ate before fansigns was dumplings too and
since dumplings are something you can eat fast I can't eat dumplings if there's no pickled radish.
I can eat without soy sauce but you need pickled radish
to really properly enjoy the taste of dumplings.
I don't really like kimchi dumplings. I'm unconditionally a meat dumpling person
Hearts are at 3 million. Man how hard is Flover overworking?
I can't even fathom it.
Suddenly I'm hungry again.
Between fried dumplings and boiled dumplings.
I don't really like fried dumplings. If they're right there I eat them fine.
I eat them fine if they're there but
I've probably bought them before. It's not like I haven't.
But usually I go for boiled dumplings.
Ah I have a festival stage later but if I eat like this my stomach will stick out
It's delicious.
I'll just take one more bite
Just one more bite
I'll stop eating. Cleanly scraping it like this
I'll eat it cleanly and mm I should stop here. Ah.
You're saying I can eat more I know.
Oh now when I eat this kind of cake
Kimchi stew or maybe soybean paste stew
it's inevitable that I crave something hot.
Yes. Wearing hoop earrings with a zip-up like this
is unbalanced.
How is it?
Turn on your blinker before coming in.
Your nails are pretty. Yeah
Ah the Knowing Bros behind-the-scenes
First of all the seniors took such good care of us
so I think it was a time where I felt things anew.
Anyway I also consider myself to have quite a few years of experience
you know. Of course
but wow the seniors really
even though they've been in the industry for so long they are so so
uh
so hard working.
Mm. Despite that
seeing them work so hard at everything made me think ah,
I need to be like that too. That's how I'll have a long run. I think I felt that way.
Really and their sense is so so good. Wow how do they save this like that?
I thought that a lot. Veterans really are different
I had those thoughts. I was a bit nervous. I was really nervous. Actually
I was very tense.
Because they took care of us I felt warm inside.
Hearts are at
4 million.
Is Flover really going crazy today?
Then is the Flover writing comments and the Flover pressing hearts separate?
You can't write comments while pressing hearts like this.
Or do you press hearts like this and then
write a comment? Or maybe
oh nevermind
Or you could just do this. Press hearts and use voice to text
Hayoung pressing hearts and using voice Hayoung
couldn't you do it like that?
Ah but if you use voice you tend to speak in short answers. So it feels stiff
everyone from now on mm
add a wave and a heart at the end of all your sentences.
Cute. Omg cute.
No. Just do whatever is comfortable. Just don't give short answers.
Ah, there's a word I don't like, should I tell you what it is?
Should I? Ah. It's actually nothing big.
Mm. I
like the word 'ung'. Honestly 'ung' and 'eung' are both fine.
But
I hate it when people go 'eong'.
'Eong' feels a bit insincere. Like what is that?
But 'eong' or 'Unnie' like that is fine but if it's just 'eong' then
it kinda feels like
that kind of vibe.
'Eung' is kinda mm
soft but 'eong' is
kinda this kind of vibe. So
I wonder why they're talking like that?
I get that thought. Is it just me?
So to Flover who say 'ung ung' I want to say yes. But if they go 'eo'
I wish Flover would just speak nicely to me.
I end up thinking like that.
'Eong' isn't really a bad expression but. Ah I don't know.
Honestly I tried really hard to like it.
For a really long time I just haven't liked 'eong'.
Because I know most people who use 'eong' absolutely don't mean it in a bad way
at all.
Or 'ang'
'ungni' and stuff like that
I like.
When I see people who speak beautifully they're so pretty I could die.
Mm. Mm. It makes me want to take care of them more and mm
give them kisses.
So if they speak beautifully mm this
person is really mm
nice. They're a good person. I think it feels like that.
So I also want to only say beautiful words as much as possible.
Ah, right. I saw the YouTube comments for Knowing Bros and
there were comments like the meeting of Kang Hodong and Song Udong. It was so
funny. This got edited out but to Hodong senior
I told him that my nickname is actually Song Udong.
Yes. Asking why it's Song Udong. But honestly I don't really know why I'm Song Udong.
So I just uh
was it because of sticking my tongue out? I think I said things like that. Honestly I don't
really remember and I just told him I have the nickname Song Udong.
Are the comments this fast only for me?
Ah, Flover feels like they're fast too, right?
Man, so many people came to wish me a happy birthday it makes me so thankful.
I'm touched.
But Flover I really have to go soon
I really have to go now.
Since I have a stage next I need to go get ready.
Thank you so so much for celebrating together with me today.
But you pressed the hearts so hard
it's at 6 million.
So relax your hands now. Your hands must hurt.
Thank you. Ah, and mm
Thank you so so much to the Flover who opened birthday cafes too. My aunts
went to the birthday cafes and sent me a lot of proof shots and stuff like that.
So ah, I was touched.
It must have been hard preparing. Mm. I saw it all through photos and videos
so thank you so so much for really preparing it.
Flover went too. You went and wished me a happy birthday a lot.
Somehow mm birthday cafes. Yeah. I toured them like this
there were a lot of Flover like that too so seeing that made me kind of proud.
Saeng-ca tour right. It's called a birthday cafe tour.
Thanks.
You spent this Chuseok holiday well too, right? Flover
I really rested so well that I wanted to work again quickly
I rested that much. I rested so much I wondered if I'd ever rested like this before and
today right after the Chuseok holiday
my birthday came and so many Flover wished me a happy birthday so I was so so
so thankful I was thankful.
I'll go and have fun performing at the Kangnam University festival stage today too.
I'll get going now. Thanks for the birthday wishes Flover.
Bye. Have a good time until the very end today
Capture time.
I'm going. Bye. Thanks.